George Lardner Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part II: Subject File, 1959-2005 (Box 289-560)
  - Domestic and family violence (Box 360)
    - Legal system, general, 1993-1998, (2 folders) (Box 365)
    - Miscellany, 1995-1999, (2 folders) (Box 365)
    - Notes, circa 1993-circa 1998 (Box 366)
    - Printed matter, 1994-1997, (2 folders) (Box 366)
    - Proposed federal victims' rights amendment, 1998-2000, (2 folders) (Box 366)
    - Research studies, 1987-1998 (Box 366)
    - Research studies, 1987-1998 (Box 367)
    - Violence Against Women Act, 1994-2000, (5 folders) (Box 367)
  - Donovan, Raymond J. (Box 368)
    - Articles, 1981-1986, (2 folders) (Box 368)
    - Attorney's fees, 1987-1988 (Box 368)
    - Bookin, Stephen, records request, 1983-1986 (Box 368)
    - Clippings, 1970-1986, (3 folders) (Box 368)
    - Confirmation hearings, 1981 (Box 368)
    - Confirmation hearings, 1981, (2 folders) (Box 369)
    - Fatico, Carmine and Daniel, hearing, 1977-1983 (Box 369)
    - FBI files (Box 369)
      - Bribery and conflicts of interest, 1980-1986 (Box 369)
      - Central records system guide, 1978 (Box 369)
      - Ethics in Government Act, 1970-1983, (3 folders) (Box 369)
      - Ethics in Government Act, 1970-1983, (7 folders) (Box 370)
      - Ethics in Government Act, 1970-1983, (3 folders) (Box 371)
      - Schiavone Construction Co., 1982-1986 (Box 371)
      - Special Inquiry Unit (SPIN) investigation, 1981-1986, (2 folders) (Box 371)
      - Special Inquiry Unit (SPIN) investigation, 1981-1986, (5 folders) (Box 372)
    - Financial disclosures, 1981-1983, (2 folders) (Box 372)
    - Freedom of Information Act requests, 1984-1990 (Box 373)
    - Friedland, David, 1980-1982 (Box 373)
    - Galiber, Joseph L., borough president campaign, 1979-1982 (Box 373)
    - General, 1981-1987, (5 folders) (Box 373)
    - Independent counsel report, 1987 (Box 374)
    - Kelly, Patrick, 1980-1982 (Box 374)
    - Kelpfer, Michael, indictment, 1979-1983 (Box 374)
    - Labor unions (Box 374)
      - Blasters, Drillrunners, and Miners Union, 1979-1982, (2 folders) (Box 374)
      - Cavalieri, Samuel, 1980-1982 (Box 374)
      - Cody, John, 1982-1983 (Box 374)
      - Cole, Joyce, 1979-1981 (Box 374)
      - Cole, Joyce, 1979-1981 (Box 375)
      - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1977-1993, (3 folders) (Box 375)
      - Laborers' International Union of North America, 1980-1981 (Box 375)
      - McCarthy, Jack, 1966-1970 (Box 375)
      - Montuoro, Mario, 1970-1982, (2 folders) (Box 375)
      - Montuoro, Mario, 1970-1982, (2 folders) (Box 376)
      - Provenzano, Nuncio and Salvatore, 1980-1982 (Box 376)
      - Sanzo, Louis, 1978-1983, (2 folders) (Box 376)
    - Mafia and organized crime, 1972-1985, (2 folders) (Box 376)
    - Masselli, Nat, 1981-1983, (2 folders) (Box 376)
    - Masselli, William, 1978-1986, (3 folders) (Box 377)
    - McGorty, Donald J., report, 1978-1985, (4 folders) (Box 377)
    - Miscellany, 1981-1985 (Box 377)
    - Mullen, Francis M., 1982-1983 (Box 378)
    - Notes, 1981-1987, (6 folders) (Box 378)
    - Notes, 1981-1987, (6 folders) (Box 379)
    - Notes, 1981-1987, (7 folders) (Box 380)
    - Notes, 1981-1987 (Box 381)
    - Operation Tumcon, 1977-1986, (6 folders) (Box 381)
    - Orlando, Michael, 1978-1985 (Box 381)
    - Orlando, Michael, 1978-1985, (2 folders) (Box 382)
    - People v. Schiavone Construction Co., et al. (Box 382)
      - Clippings, 1986-1987 (Box 382)
      - Gag order, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 382)
      - General, 1986, (3 folders) (Box 382)
      - General, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 383)
      - Jurors, 1986-1987, (2 folders) (Box 383)
      - Legal documents, 1986-1987 (Box 383)
      - Notes, 1986-1987, (3 folders) (Box 383)
      - Notes, 1986-1987, (8 folders) (Box 384)
      - Suppression hearings, 1985 (Box 384)
      - Trial exhibits, 1979 (Box 385)
      - Trial transcripts, 1986-1987, (3 folders) (Box 385)
      - Gallo, Mario, 1969-1982 (Box 385)
      - Miscellany, 1976-1987 (Box 385)
      - New York City subway, 1980-1986 (Box 385)
      - New York City subway, 1980-1986, (2 folders) (Box 386)
      - Schiavone v. Montuoro, 1982-1983, (2 folders) (Box 386)
      - Subcontractors, 1969-1983, (4 folders) (Box 386)
      - Suspension hearing, 1985 (Box 387)
    - Silverman, Leon, 1981-1987, (3 folders) (Box 387)
    - U.S. House of Representatives, Committee on the Judiciary, 1979-1982 (Box 387)
    - U.S. Senate Committee on Labor and Human Resources, 1981-1982, (2 folders) (Box 387)
    - Webster, William, 1982-1985 (Box 387)
  - Environmental issues (Box 388)
    - 3M Company and Scotchgard, 1997-2001, (2 folders) (Box 388)
    - Court decisions, 1986-2000 (Box 388)
    - DuPont and Al Gore, 1992-2000 (Box 388)
    - General, 1987-1989 (Box 388)
    - Judicial junkets, 1998-2000 (Box 388)
    - Oil spill, Santa Barbara, Calif. (Box 388)
      - Article drafts, 1969, (2 folders) (Box 388)
      - Miscellany, 1969 (Box 388)
      - Notes, 1969 (Box 388)
      - Notes, 1969, (3 folders) (Box 389)
      - Press releases, 1969 (Box 389)
    - Pesticides (Box 389)
      - General, 1986-2000, (5 folders) (Box 389)
      - General, 1986-2000, (4 folders) (Box 390)
      - Methyl bromide and chlorofluorocarbons, 1986-2000, (4 folders) (Box 390)
      - Methyl bromide and chlorofluorocarbons, 1986-2000 (Box 391)
      - Pombo, Richard and Regulatory Fairness and Openness Act, 1999-2000 (Box 391)
  - Espy, Mike, ethics investigation, 1994-1998, (2 folders) (Box 391)
  - Essex, Mark, New Orleans, La. sniper, 1972-1973, (2 folders) (Box 391)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box 391)
    - Black bag jobs, 1981 (Box 391)
    - Hoover, J. Edgar, secret files, 1975, (2 folders) (Box 391)
    - Lamphere, Robert, 1977-1986 (Box 391)
    - Lindblom, Lance, Freedom of Information Act request lawsuit, 1994-1998 (Box 391)
    - Miscellany, 1996-2003 (Box 391)
    - Top echelon informants, Boston, Mass., 1998 (Box 391)
  - Immigration (Box 391)
    - Domestic violence asylum policy, 2000-2003 (Box 391)
    - Domestic violence asylum policy, 2000-2003 (Box 392)
    - General, 1992-2003, (7 folders) (Box 392)
    - General, 1992-2003, (3 folders) (Box 393)
    - Higher education, 2002-2003 (Box 393)
    - Notes, circa 2003 (Box 393)
    - Sex trafficking, 1998 (Box 393)
  - Independent council act (Ethics in Government Act expiration) (Box 393)
    - Dash, Samuel, resignation as ethics advisor to Kenneth Starr, 1984-1998 (Box 393)
    - General, 1992-2000 (Box 393)
    - General, 1992-2000, (8 folders) (Box 394)
    - General, 1992-2000, (5 folders) (Box 395)
    - Georgetown University symposium, Washington, D.C., 1998, (2 folders) (Box 395)
    - Morrison v. Olson, 1988 (Box 396)
    - Notes, circa 1999 (Box 396)
    - U.S. Senate Judiciary subcommittee hearing (impeachment vs. indictment), 1975-1998, (2 folders) (Box 396)
    - Watergate Affair, 1999, (3 folders) (Box 396)
  - Indian gambling and casinos (Box 396)
    - Burton Commission data, 1995-1998 (Box 396)
    - California tribes, dispute regarding illegal gaming machines, 1998, (6 folders) (Box 397)
    - Chippewa tribes, rejection of Hudson, Wis., casino application (Box 397)
      - Articles, 1995-1998 (Box 397)
      - Articles, 1995-1998, (2 folders) (Box 398)
      - Babbitt, Bruce E., investigation by Carol Elder Bruce, 1979-2001, (3 folders) (Box 398)
      - Babbitt, Bruce E., and Paul Eckstein, 1995-1998, (2 folders) (Box 398)
      - Background material, 1994-1996, (2 folders) (Box 398)
      - Christy, Arthur, 1998 (Box 398)
      - Freeh, Louis J., perjury investigation, 1997-1998 (Box 398)
      - General, 1983-1999, (6 folders) (Box 399)
      - General, 1983-1999, (7 folders) (Box 400)
      - General, 1983-1999, (6 folders) (Box 401)
      - Government and lobbyists documents, 1995-1997 (Box 401)
      - Government and lobbyists documents, 1995-1997, (7 folders) (Box 402)
      - Government and lobbyists documents, 1995-1997, (5 folders) (Box 403)
      - Grobmyer, Mark, U.S. Senate depositions, 1997, (3 folders) (Box 403)
      - Grobmyer, Mark, U.S. Senate depositions, 1997, (3 folders) (Box 404)
      - Ickes, Harold M., 1995-1999, (4 folders) (Box 404)
      - Indian Gaming Regulatory Act, proposed amendments, 1998 (Box 404)
      - Indian Gaming Regulatory Act, proposed amendments, 1998, (3 folders) (Box 405)
      - Lobbyists' depositions, 1995-1997, (3 folders) (Box 405)
      - Notes, 1997-1998 (Box 405)
      - Shakopee Mdewakanton Sioux tribe trust application, 1998, (3 folders) (Box 405)
      - U.S. House of Representatives, Committee on Government Reform and Oversight, hearings, 1986-1998, (6 folders) (Box 406)
      - U.S. House of Representatives, Committee on Government Reform and Oversight, hearings, 1986-1998, (6 folders) (Box 407)
      - U.S. House of Representatives, Committee on Government Reform and Oversight, hearings, 1986-1998, (7 folders) (Box 408)
    - Mashantucket Pequot tribe, expansion of Connecticut reservation, 1995-1998, (2 folders) (Box 409)
  - Iran-Contra Affair (Box 409)
    - Classified Information Procedures Act, 1983-1988, (4 folders) (Box 409)
    - Clippings, 1987-1992, (2 folders) (Box 409)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 410)
    - Data, 1986-1987 (Box 410)
    - Fiers, Alan Dale, 1991 (Box 410)
    - General, 1975-1992, (4 folders) (Box 410)
    - George, Clair E. (Box 410)
      - Clippings, 1992 (Box 410)
      - Legal documents (Box 410)
        - Bench and chambers transcripts, 1992 (Box 410)
        - General, 1992 (Box 410)
        - Indictments, jurors, pretrial orders, 1987-1992, (2 folders) (Box 411)
        - Jury instructions, 1992 (Box 411)
        - Pretrial motions, second trial, 1992 (Box 411)
        - Trial transcripts, 1992, (5 folders) (Box 411)
        - Trial transcripts, 1992, (8 folders) (Box 412)
        - Trial transcripts, 1992, (7 folders) (Box 413)
        - Trial transcripts, 1992, (4 folders) (Box 414)
      - Notes, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 414)
      - Trial exhibits, 1984-1992, (3 folders) (Box 414)
    - Ghorbanifar, Manncher, operation, 1986 (Box 415)
    - Intelligence reform, 1991-1992 (Box 415)
    - Miscellany, 1974-1992, (4 folders) (Box 415)
    - North, Oliver (Box 415)
      - Clippings, 1986-1996, (3 folders) (Box 415)
      - General, 1974-1989 (Box 415)
      - General, 1974-1989, (4 folders) (Box 416)
      - Legal documents (Box 416)
        - Bench conferences, 1989, (3 folders) (Box 416)
        - Jurors and miscellany, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 417)
        - Jury instructions, 1989, (4 folders) (Box 417)
        - Motions, orders, memoranda, exhibits, 1989-1991, (3 folders) (Box 417)
        - Sentencing transcript, 1989 (Box 418)
        - Trial transcripts, 1989, (7 folders) (Box 418)
        - Trial transcripts, 1989, (7 folders) (Box 419)
        - Trial transcripts, 1989, (7 folders) (Box 420)
        - Trial transcripts, 1989, (7 folders) (Box 421)
        - Trial transcripts, 1989, (7 folders) (Box 422)
        - Trial transcripts, 1989, (7 folders) (Box 423)
        - Trial transcripts, 1989, (7 folders) (Box 424)
        - Trial transcripts, 1989, (7 folders) (Box 425)
        - Trial transcripts, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 426)
      - Notes, 1989 (Box 426)
      - Trial exhibits (Box 426)
        - Defense, 1984-1989, (5 folders) (Box 426)
        - Prosecution, 1984-1989, (6 folders) (Box 427)
        - Prosecution letters, 1985, (2 folders) (Box 427)
    - Owen, Robert W., memoranda, 1985-1995, (3 folders) (Box 428)
    - Pardons, 1992-1993 (Box 428)
    - Peres, Shimon, 1985-1988 (Box 428)
    - Project Elephant Herd, 1984-2000 (Box 428)
    - Reports (Box 428)
      - Christic Institute, 1987-1988 (Box 428)
      - Congressional committees, 1987 (Box 428)
      - Independent counsel, 1993-1994, (3 folders) (Box 429)
      - President's Special Review Board, 1987 (Box 429)
      - Tower commission, 1987-1988, (2 folders) (Box 429)
    - United States v. Poindexter, et al., 1988 (Box 429)
    - United States v. Poindexter, et al., 1988, (5 folders) (Box 430)
    - Walsh, Lawrence E. (Box 430)
      - Clippings, 1987-1991 (Box 430)
      - General, 1989-1997 (Box 430)
      - Notes, 1987-1992 (Box 430)
    - Weinberger, Caspar W. (Box 430)
      - Clippings, 1992 (Box 430)
      - "For Their Eyes Only," report by the Center for Public Integrity, 1992 (Box 430)
      - General, 1982-1993 (Box 430)
      - General, 1982-1993, (7 folders) (Box 431)
      - General, 1982-1993 (Box 432)
      - Notes, 1992 (Box 432)
      - Trial exhibits, 1992 (Box 432)
  - Iraq (Box 432)
    - Banca Nazionale del Lavoro (BNL) (Box 432)
      - Beneficiaries, 1992 (Box 432)
      - Germany and France, 1992 (Box 432)
      - González, Henry B., 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 432)
      - Iraq policy, 1992, (2 folders) (Box 432)
      - Italian Commission, circa 1991 (Box 433)
      - Kane, Dennis, notes, circa 1992 (Box 433)
      - Kennametal Inc., 1990-1992 (Box 433)
      - Prewar Iraq policy, 1990-1992, (6 folders) (Box 433)
      - Prewar Iraq policy, 1990-1992, (8 folders) (Box 434)
      - Prewar Iraq policy, 1990-1992, (8 folders) (Box 435)
      - Whitley, Joe D., 1992 (Box 436)
    - Brennan, Jack, 1992 (Box 436)
    - Bull, Gerald, 1990-1992 (Box 436)
    - Cardoen, Carlos, 1991-1992 (Box 436)
    - Clippings, 1992 (Box 436)
    - General, 1988-1992 (Box 436)
    - General Accounting Office reports, 1988-1991 (Box 436)
    - Independent counsel, 1992-1993 (Box 436)
    - Memo from Lardner, circa 1992 (Box 436)
    - Mitsui and Co., 1992 (Box 436)
    - National Security Directive 26, 1991 (Box 436)
    - Notes, circa 1991 (Box 436)
    - Patriot missile, 1991-1992 (Box 436)
    - Patriot missile, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 437)
    - Photographs, Gerald Bull, undated (Box 437)
    - Safair freights, 1991 (Box 437)
    - Soghanalian, Sarkis (Box 437)
      - Articles, 1992 (Box 437)
      - Lawsuits, 1990-1992 (Box 437)
      - Legal documents, 1987-1992, (3 folders) (Box 437)
      - Miscellany, 1992 (Box 437)
      - Moreno, Federico Antonio, circa 1992 (Box 437)
      - Notes, 1992, (2 folders) (Box 438)
      - Prison interview, 1992, (8 folders) (Box 438)
    - U.S. foreign policy, current documents, 1982-1989 (Box 438)
  - Jonestown, Guyana, and Mark Lane, 1977-1979, (4 folders) (Box 439)
  - Kennedy, Edward, Chappaquiddick Island, Mass., incident (Box 439)
    - Article drafts. 1969 (Box 439)
    - Clippings, 1969, (4 folders) (Box 439)
    - Edward M. Kennedy v. James A. Boyle, 1969 (Box 439)
    - Twentieth anniversary, 1989 (Box 439)
  - Kennedy, John F., assassination See also Containers 536-538, United States House of Representatives, Select Committee on Assassinations (Box 439)
    - Acoustics, 1988, 1993 (Box 439)
    - Aguilar, Gary L., 1998-1999 (Box 439)
    - Alternate theories, 1978-2001 (Box 439)
    - Alternate theories, 1978-2001, (2 folders) (Box 440)
    - Articles by Lardner, 1977-1997, (3 folders) (Box 440)
    - Bullet fragments test, 2000 (Box 440)
    - CBS News documentary, Who Killed JFK: The Final Chapter?, 1993 (Box 440)
    - Contact list, circa 1993 (Box 440)
    - Correspondence (Box 440)
      - General, 1967, 1975-1984, 1993, (4 folders) (Box 440)
      - General, 1993-2000, (2 folders) (Box 441)
      - Weisberg, Harold, 1991-1993 (Box 441)
    - Exner, Judith, interview notes, 1991-1993, (3 folders) (Box 441)
    - Garrison, Jim (Box 441)
      - Ferrie, David, 1967 (Box 441)
      - Gaming violations investigation, 1971 (Box 441)
      - Miscellany, 1967-1968 (Box 441)
      - Russo, Perry, tapes, 1992-2005 (Box 441)
      - Shaw, Clay, arrest and trial, 1967-1969, (6 folders) (Box 442)
    - Halpern, Sam, interview notes, 1993 (Box 442)
    - Hersh, Seymour, The Dark Side of Camelot, 1997-1998 (Box 442)
    - Hersh, Seymour, The Dark Side of Camelot, 1997-1998 (Box 443)
    - Hoch, Paul L., 1980-1993 (Box 443)
    - Hosty, James P., interview notes, 1992-1993 (Box 443)
    - JFK, film directed by Oliver Stone, 1991-1992, (4 folders) (Box 443)
    - JFK, film directed by Oliver Stone, 1991-1992, (6 folders) (Box 444)
    - JFK, film directed by Oliver Stone, 1991-1992, (6 folders) (Box 445)
    - JFK, film directed by Oliver Stone, 1991-1992, (8 folders) (Box 446)
    - JFK, film directed by Oliver Stone, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 447)
    - Lifton, David, interview transcript, circa 1993 (Box 447)
    - Morley, Jefferson, articles, 1993 (Box 447)
    - Nechiporenko, Oleg, 1993 (Box 447)
    - Notes, 1991-1993, undated, (6 folders) (Box 447)
    - Posner, Gerald L., 1993, 2000 (Box 448)
    - President John F. Kennedy Assassination Records Collection Act of 1992 (Box 448)
      - Assassination Records Review Board (Box 448)
        - Angleton, James, 1997 (Box 448)
        - Autopsy testimony, 1997-1998, (2 folders) (Box 448)
        - Boswell, J. Thornton, deposition, 1996, (2 folders) (Box 448)
        - Cuba policy records, 1997-1998, (2 folders) (Box 448)
        - Groden, Robert J., deposition, 1996 (Box 449)
        - Medical exhibits, 1996, (3 folders) (Box 449)
        - Nominees, 1994 (Box 449)
        - Records regarding Kennedy's brain, 1998 (Box 449)
        - Records release, 1993-1997, (3 folders) (Box 449)
        - Records release, 1997-1999, (5 folders) (Box 450)
        - Sheridan, Nancy, subpoena, 1997 (Box 450)
      - Effectiveness, 1993, (2 folders) (Box 450)
      - Legislation, 1992, (3 folders) (Box 451)
      - Subpoenas, 1997 (Box 451)
    - Press and clippings, 1963-1992, (5 folders) (Box 451)
    - Press and clippings, 1993-2002, (6 folders) (Box 452)
    - Research material (Box 452)
      - Autopsy records, 1962-1996, (2 folders) (Box 452)
      - Autopsy records, 1962-1996, (6 folders) (Box 453)
      - Autopsy records, 1962-1996, (4 folders) (Box 454)
      - Central Intelligence Agency (Box 454)
        - Mexico City, Mexico, 1963-1964, (2 folders) (Box 454)
        - Miscellany, 1960-1967 (Box 454)
        - Miscellany, 1960-1967, (6 folders) (Box 455)
        - Oswald, Lee Harvey, Personality (201) file, 1959-1967, 1993, (3 folders) (Box 455)
        - Oswald, Lee Harvey, personality (201) file, 1959-1967, 1993, (7 folders) (Box 456)
        - Oswald, Lee Harvey, personality (201) file, 1959-1967, 1993, (7 folders) (Box 457)
        - Oswald, Lee Harvey, personality (201) file, 1959-1967, 1993, (7 folders) (Box 458)
        - Oswald, Lee Harvey, personality (201) file, 1959-1967, 1993, (4 folders) (Box 459)
      - Church Committee, 1966-1976, 1995-2000 See also Containers 338-340, Select Committee to Study Government Operations with Respect to Intelligence Activities (Church Committee) (Box 459)
      - Clothing worn at time of death, photographs, 1993 (Box 459)
      - Cuba, foreign relations, 1961-1962, 1997 (Box 459)
      - DeLoach, Cartha, 1962-1979 (Box 459)
      - Ford, Gerald R. (Box 459)
        - Congressional papers, 1963-1974, (2 folders) (Box 459)
        - Congressional papers, 1963-1974, (2 folders) (Box 460)
        - Warren Commission and Jack Ruby files, 1964, (4 folders) (Box 460)
      - Hoover, J. Edgar, logs, 1960-1961, (3 folders) (Box 460)
      - Hoover, J. Edgar, logs, 1960-1961, (7 folders) (Box 461)
      - Johnson, Lyndon Baines (Box 461)
        - Cabinet papers, 1963 (Box 461)
        - Clark, Ramsey, papers, 1967 (Box 461)
        - Memoranda, 1963, (2 folders) (Box 461)
        - National Security Agency files, 1963-1964 (Box 462)
        - Pearson, Drew, papers, 1960-1964 (Box 462)
        - Telephone call notes, 1963 (Box 462)
        - Telephone call transcripts, 1963, (4 folders) (Box 462)
        - Telephone call transcripts, 1963, (3 folders) (Box 463)
      - Joint Chiefs of Staff records, 1963, (4 folders) (Box 463)
      - Kennedy, John F., President's Office files, 1961-1963, (2 folders) (Box 464)
      - Mexico City, Mexico, FBI report and Warren Commission trip, 1963-1964, (3 folders) (Box 464)
      - National Archives and Records Administration, miscellaneous records, 1961-1976, (4 folders) (Box 464)
      - National Security Agency records, 1963 (Box 465)
      - Oswald, Lee Harvey, 1960-1996, (4 folders) (Box 465)
      - Photographs of Dallas, Tex., on Nov. 22, 1963 (Box 465)
      - Ruby, Jack, 1963, (4 folders) (Box 465)
      - Russell, Richard B., 1963-1967, 1993 (Box 465)
      - U.S. Army Commands records, 1963, (2 folders) (Box 466)
      - U.S. House Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA) (Box 466)
        - Legislation, 1976 (Box 466)
        - Miscellany, 1977-1991 (Box 466)
        - McKeown, Robert Ray, testimony, 1978, (2 folders) (Box 466)
        - Report on Lee Harvey Oswald, the CIA, and Mexico City, 1978 (Box 466)
        - Report on Lee Harvey Oswald, the CIA, and Mexico City, 1978, (2 folders) (Box 467)
      - Yeltsin, Boris Nikolayevich, papers regarding assassination, 1999, (3 folders) (Box 467)
    - Revill, Jack, interview notes, 1993 (Box 467)
    - Ruby, Jack, 1993 (Box 467)
    - Russo, Gus, Live by the Sword, 1998 (Box 467)
    - Warren Commission (Box 467)
      - Basic source material list, 1968 (Box 467)
      - Ford, Gerald R., edits to report, 1997 (Box 468)
      - Time line, circa 1993 (Box 468)
    - Zapruder film, 1993-2001, (7 folders) (Box 468)
  - Kennedy, Robert F. (Box 468)
    - Assassination (Box 468)
      - Research material (Box 468)
        - Arab-American organizations, 1966-1969, undated, (2 folders) (Box 468)
        - Newspaper clippings, 1968, (2 folders) (Box 469)
        - Periodicals, 1968-1969, undated (Box 469)
    - Sirhan, Sirhan trial (Box 469)
      - Articles, 1969, undated, (7 folders) (Box 469)
      - Correspondence (Box 470)
        - General, 1968-1969, undated (Box 470)
        - Personal, 1969, undated (Box 470)
      - Notes, undated (Box 470)
      - Notebooks, 1968-1969, undated, (3 folders) (Box 470)
      - Notebooks, 1968-1969, undated, (3 folders) (Box 471)
      - Notebooks, 1968-1969, undated (Box 472)
      - Reporters' daily transcript, 1969, (6 folders) (Box 472)
      - Reporters' daily transcript, 1969, (3 folders) (Box 473)
      - Research material (Box 473)
        - Articles, 1959, 1968-1969, undated, (3 folders) (Box 473)
        - Legal documents, 1968-1969 (Box 473)
        - Miscellany, 1954-1969, undated, (3 folders) (Box 474)
      - Trial transcript, 1969, (2 folders) (Box 474)
      - Weekly summaries, 1968-1969, (2 folders) (Box 474)
      - Weekly summaries, 1968-1969 (Box 475)
  - Labor unions (Box 475)
    - AFL-CIO (Box 475)
      - Democratic National Committee, suppression of records, 1996-2001, (4 folders) (Box 475)
      - Toll-free telephone calls, 1997 (Box 475)
    - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, money laundering, 1997 (Box 475)
    - Laborers' International Union of North America, 1996 (Box 475)
    - United States vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, deposition of Jim Moody, 1989 (Box 475)
    - United States vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, deposition of Jim Moody, 1989 (Box 476)
    - Yablonski family murders and United Mine Workers complicity, 1969-1972, (3 folders) (Box 476)
  - Lanier, David W., 1992-1996, (3 folders) (Box 476)
  - Livingston, Bob, resignation, 1998 (Box 476)
  - McConnell, Mitch (Box 476)
    - Articles, 1997 (Box 476)
    - Index, 1997 (Box 476)
    - Notes, 1997, (5 folders) (Box 477)
    - Questions, 1997 (Box 477)
    - Research binders and materials, 1997, (6 folders) (Box 477)
    - Research binders and materials, 1997, (8 folders) (Box 478)
    - Research binders and materials, 1997, (8 folders) (Box 479)
  - Meese, Edwin (Box 479)
    - Attorney general nomination, 1984-1987 (Box 479)
    - Financial disclosure, 1987 (Box 479)
    - Inslaw, Inc. (firm), 1987 (Box 479)
    - Independent counsel report, 1984 (Box 480)
    - Whittlesey, Faith Ryan, 1986-1988 (Box 480)